http://www.wanigas.com/privacy-security-disclosures

Important Member Updates and Membership Help Information Regarding the Coronavirus (COVID-19) - Click here to learn more.
Close Alert
Important Notice: System maintenance is scheduled beginning 10pm, Saturday, December 12th through 12pm (noon), Sunday, December 13th. Click Here for Details.
Close Alert
Privacy, Security & Disclosures
Home > About Wanigas > Privacy, Security & Disclosures
Privacy Notice
Important Information About Your Privacy Notice.
We, our, and us, when used in this notice, mean Wanigas Credit Union.
This is our privacy notice for our members. When we use the words "you" and "your" we mean the following types of members:
Our consumer members who have a continuing relationship by purchasing or holding financial products or services such as a(n):
Share account
Loan account
Credit card account
Automobile lease we service
Mortgage brokerage services
Former members
We will tell you the sources of the information we collect about you. We will tell you what measures we take to secure that information.
We will tell you what information we share about you with other entities. We will explain what your rights are, and how you can exercise them. If you share an account relationship with someone else, such as a joint account holder or co-borrower, we suggest that you share this information with such persons to ensure that each of you is aware of our policy and your options.
We first define some terms.
Nonpublic personal information means information about you that we collect in connection with providing a financial product or service to you. Nonpublic personal information does not include information that is available from public sources, such as telephone directories or government records. Hereafter, we will use the term "information" to mean nonpublic personal information as defined in this section.
An affiliate is a company we own or control.
A nonaffiliated third party is a person we do not employ or a company that is not an affiliate of ours. This is also known as nonaffiliated third party, or simply, an "other party."
THE INFORMATION WE COLLECT
We collect information about you from the following sources:
Information you give us on applications or other forms
Information about your transactions with us
Information about your transactions with other parties
Information from a consumer reporting agency
THE CONFIDENTIALITY, SECURITY, AND INTEGRITY OF YOUR INFORMATION
We restrict access to information about you to those employees who need to know that information to provide products or services to you. We maintain physical, electronic, and procedural safeguards to protect this information.
YOUR INFORMATION AND OTHER PARTIES
We may disclose information to other parties. Here are the kinds of information we disclose to these other parties:
Information you give us on an application or other forms, such as:
Name
Address
Types of Other Parties
We may disclose information about you to the following types of other parties:
Financial service providers, such as:
Insurance agents
We may also disclose information about you to other parties as permitted by law.
Reasons For Disclosing
We may disclose information about you to other parties to provide you with information about additional products and services.
INFORMATION ABOUT FORMER MEMBERS
We have the same policy about disclosing information about former members as we do about current members.
Click Here to review the Wanigas Privacy Disclosure
Go to main navigation
Related Links
Links
Privacy Notice
Electronic Fund Transfers (EFT) Agreement and Disclosure
Funds Availability Disclosure
VISA Rate Disclosure
ATM Locations
HomeLoan & CreditLoan & Credit HomeAuto LoansRecreational Vehicle LoansMotorcycle LoansMortgage LoansBoat LoansHome Equity LoansPersonal LoansPersonal Loans HomeHoliday LoanVISA Credit CardVISA Credit Card HomeCredit Union Give Back SweepstakesVISA Credit Card (Copy)$25 Online Loan App PromotionChecking & SavingsChecking & Savings HomeChecking AccountsChecking Accounts HomeSwitch To WanigasSavings AccountsMoney MarketCertificate of DepositIRAsATM/Debit CardsATM/Debit Cards HomeCard Skimmers - Tips You Need to KnowDirect DepositDirect Deposit HomeHelpful Tax TipsOnline/Convenience ServicesOnline/Convenience Services HomeOnline BankingOnline Banking Homee-Banking VideosMobile BankingMobile Banking HomeMobile Check DepositDigital WalletsOnline PaymentsEZ Telephone Bankinge-Alertse-StatementsApplicationsReorder ChecksMember ResourcesMember Resources HomeCalculatorsFinancial Resource CenterFraud TipsFREE Credit Report ReviewGift Cards/Prepaid CardsGreenPath Financial WellnessInsurance Claim PortalMember DiscountsMortgage RatesRatesTruStage InsuranceYouth ServicesAbout WanigasAbout Wanigas HomeOverviewMembershipHours & LocationsATM LocationsNews & EventsNews & Events HomeImproved Online Banking Coronavirus (COVID-19)NewslettersPrivacy/Security/DisclosuresWanigas Official FamilyNominations for Board of Directors CareersMember Success Stories
